Guide to the Guide to the Civil Service Technical Guild Records WAG.024
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X: Women's Committee, 1985-2007
  - Events: Take Our Daughters to Work Day, Apr 1993 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Events: "Oh No You Don't" (Year 8), 1994 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Events: Actions for Women's Health (Year 9), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Events: Womens Work, Past and Present (Year 10), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Events: Women's Work II (Year 11), 1997 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Events: Women's Work III (Year 12), 1998 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Events, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Logo, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Northeast Summer Institute Participation, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Organizing the Committee, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Publicity, 1986-1999 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Series XI: Unprocessed Material
  - Unprocessed Material (Box 19, Box 20, Box 21)
  - Cartoons by Steve Beck, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 005, Folder 3)
  - Philip Brueck papers, 1920-1985 (Box Shared Tamiment 016, Folder 2, Box Shared Tamiment 014, Folder 5, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Folder 1-13)
- Series XII: Archived Website, Mar 5, 2009-ongoing
  Scope and Content Note
  The Civil Service Technical Guild (Local 375, DC 37), founded in 1929, represents 7,000 engineers, architects, scientists, chemists, planners, and other technical inspectors working for the City of New York. The guild's goals include the prevention of the outsourcing city contracts, fighting for the adherence to civil service laws, enforcing contracts, and fighting privatization. The union is affiliated with the ASFCME and the AFL-CIO. The website contains news listings, their newsletter, Local 375 Update, event listings, contracts, and job descriptions.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.